Guide to the Duke University Archives Photographic Negative Collection, 1855-1995
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
Duke University Archives Photographic Negative collection 1855-1995
University Archives, Duke University
Duke University. University Archives
19.5 Linear Feet 36,750 Items
This collection consists of original and copy negatives taken by various sources over several decades. Most of the negatives were produced by the Office of News and Communication's News Bureau in the early years of Duke University and later by University Photography (upon its establishment).
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Duke University Archives Photographic Negative Collection were received by the University Archives as transfers over a period of time from various sources.
Historical Note
Most of the negatives were produced by the Office of News and Communication's News Bureau in the early years of Duke University and later by University Photography (upon its establishment). The Office of News and Communication continues to work with the news media and others to highlight the activities of Duke's faculty, students and staff while University Photography documents the people and programs of Duke University, providing high-quality images for departments, special events, sports programs, the news media and others.
Collection Overview
Contains negatives and some matching prints of University-related subjects, including people (i.e. faculty, trustees, students, etc.), buildings, construction, schools and departments. While dates range from 1855-1995, it is necessary to note that the majority of the negatives are copy negatives, rather than originals. While a good number of original negatives are included in this collection, the user should be aware that some of the corresponding dates refer to when the copy negative was made, not when the original picture was taken. In most cases, it is noted on the negative sleeve if the negative is a copy or an original. Furthermore, users should be aware that some negatives are of published material. For instance, several pages from the Chanticleer and the Chronicle were photographed and the negatives were kept. On some of the sleeves, users will find notes presumably made by the photographer regarding print quality.
An attempt was made to bring a cohesiveness to the negative collection for easier patron and staff access. The negatives are arranged in the following series: Subject Negatives, General Negatives, Building Negatives, Construction Negatives, Faculty Negatives, Medical Center Negatives, and Numbered Negatives. The Numbered Negatives are copy negatives pulled from the larger University Archives Photograph Collection. Any future additions to the negative collection will follow the numbering format.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Construction
Duke University -- Administration
Duke University -- Alumni
Duke University -- Athletics
Duke University. Board of Trustees
Duke University -- Buildings
Duke University -- Faculty
Duke University -- History
Duke University. Hospital
Duke University. Libraries
Duke University -- Students
Duke University. Trinity College of Arts and Sciences
Duke University. Woman's College
Duke, Washington, 1820-1905
Duke, Benjamin Newton, 1855-1929
Duke, James Buchanan, 1856-1925
Duke Family
Duke Homestead (Durham, N.C.)
Sarah P. Duke Gardens
Trinity College (Durham, N.C.)
Trinity College (Randolph County, N.C.)
Related Material
Duke University Archives Photograph Collection
Duke University Archives
Duke University Medical Center Archives Photograph Collection
Duke University Medical Center Archives
Contents of Collection
- Subject Negatives
  - Subject: Administration and Staff (Box 1)
    - Administration/Staff, Norm and lamp, 1958
    - Administration/Staff, Sims retirement, 1955 March
    - Administration/Staff, Brodgen, retired gardener, 1956 August
    - Administration/Staff, Frank Wall, African-American who bequeathed $100 to Duke, 1946 July
    - Administration/Staff, Jackson at work, 1957 March
    - Administration/Staff, Earl Mangum, maintenance, 1963 February
    - Administration/Staff, PS Carter, 1950 April 21
    - Administration/Staff, R. Honeycutt, retiring, 1956 April
    - Administration/Staff, personnel awards at Angus Barn, 1970 June
    - Administration/Staff, TIP, 1985 February
    - Administration/Staff, Miss Howell, Retirement Dinner
    - Administration/Staff, Party for Mrs. Pegram and Anne Garrard, 1964 August
    - Administration/Staff, Alumni Office Personnel, 1937
    - Administration/Staff, University Archives Planning Staff, 1968 January
    - Administration/Staff, Business Administration Office, Haywood and Employees, 1955 September
    - Administration/Staff, Women Deans, East Campus, 1968 January
    - Administration/Staff, Development Meeting, 1949 June
    - Administration/Staff, Development Program Luncheon, 1950 July
    - Administration/Staff, Development Program Administrators, 1950 February
    - Administration/Staff, Development Program Student Dinner, 1951 May 2
    - Administration/Staff, Development Program, Durham County Officers, 1951 February 22
    - Administration/Staff, Development Program, 1951 January 30
    - Administration/Staff, Plan for Development Office, 1963 March
    - Administration/Staff, Development Program Group Shot, 1951 November 25
    - Administration/Staff, Development Program
    - Administration/Staff, General Maintenance, 1961
    - Administration/Staff, Maids Cleaning, 1958 September
    - Administration/Staff, Spring Story from the Alumni Register, 1962 April
    - Administration/Staff, Maintenance, Alumni Register, 1957 July
    - Administration/Staff, Maintenance, Maids and Janitors, 1930s
    - Administration/Staff, Personnel Color Slides, 1969 December
    - Administration/Staff, Public Relations Department
    - Administration/Staff, New Assistant Registrar, 1960 May
    - Administration/Staff, Secretaries, including Mrs. Becky Knight, Nancy Roberson (Mrs. Dwight Stuessy), Elizabeth Aldridge (Mrs. Alfred J. Henderson), Aurelia Adams (Mrs. Charles Dukes), 1935
    - Tuthill and New Employees, 1956 September
    - Administration/Staff, Trustees, 1938-1941
    - Administration/Staff, University Officials, Alumni Register, 1954 December
    - Administration/Staff, Student Work Program, 1974 July
    - Administration/Staff, Alumni Register Cover, Archie and Christmas Mail, 1954 November
    - Administration/Staff, Training Program Employees, 1967 April
    - Administration/Staff, Employee Training, 1971 April
    - Administration/Staff, Employees, awards, cost-improvement program, 1970 December
    - Administration/Staff, Employees, retirement, 1968 June
    - Administration/Staff, Employees, training and development program, 1967 November
    - Administration/Staff, Employees, training, 1969 September
    - Administration/Staff, gifts to retiring employees, 1978
    - Administration/Staff, Employees, 30 and 40 year awards, 1972 May
    - Administration/Staff, Mrs. Persons, retirement dinner, 1971 August
    - Administration/Staff, Ted Man and staff, 1948 November 2
    - Administration/Staff, Executive Committee, identified, 1941 April 30
    - Administration/Staff, East Campus Deans, 1964 March
    - Administration/Staff, preview group photos, 1987 June
    - Administration/Staff, summer transition group, 1977 August
    - Administration/Staff, summer transition group, 1980 July
    - Administration/Staff, summer transition group, 1986 July
    - Administration/Staff, tel-com group, 1979 July
    - Administration/Staff, personnel group, 1980 December
    - Administration/Staff, Black Affairs, Gene Banks and group, 1978 January
    - Administration/Staff, Black Affairs, STP, 1978 August
    - Administration/Staff, Black Affairs, STP, 1985 June
    - Administration/Staff, Black Affairs, STP, 1979 July
    - Administration/Staff, Black Affairs, STP, 1979 July
    - Administration/Staff, Black Affairs, STP, 1981 June
    - Administration/Staff, Black Affairs, STP, 1983 June
  - Subject: Air Force ROTC
    - AFROTC, staff, 1963
    - AFROTC, chaplains, 1965 July
    - AFROTC, award to Dr. James Price, 1972 June
    - AFROTC, award to Col. Dutton, 1975 October
    - AFROTC, Arnold Air Society, 1964 February
    - AFROTC, Commissioning Exercise, 2nd Lt. Southam, AFROTC, 1969 January
    - AFROTC, 1964 June
    - AFROTC, Major Wilson and Honor St., AROTC, 1964 May
    - AFROTC, End of Year Awards, 1965 May
    - AFROTC, 1965 July
    - AFROTC, Promotion of Maj. H.M. Pollock, 1968 March
    - AFROTC, Award, 1964 May
    - AFROTC, Col. Slagel Presenting Award to Capt. Wilson, 1964 July
    - AFROTC, Award, 1967 May
    - AFROTC, Navy and Army Awards to Lt. Cmdr Lecky, 1968 December
    - AFROTC, Inspection, 1952 April 7
    - AFROTC, Freedoms Foundation Award and Col. Oldham's Promotion, 1965 May
    - AFROTC, 1950 April 24
    - AFROTC Medal Winner Award, 1950 May 8
    - AFROTC, 1950 November
    - AFROTC, 1950 November
    - AFROTC, Community Team, 1951 October 4
    - AFROTC, Graduation, 1951 June
    - AFROTC, New Officers, 1951 September
    - AFROTC, Review of Visiting Officers, 1951 March 19
    - AFROTC, 1952 May
    - AFROTC, 1952 February
    - AFROTC, Air Medal to Oxford Mother, 1952 September
    - AFROTC, Commissioning, 1952 January 29
    - AFROTC, Swearing In, 1952 June 1
    - AFROTC, 1953 March
    - AFROTC, Inspection Team, 1953 May
    - AFROTC, Air Force School Conference, 1953 June 20
    - AFROTC, Competition, 1953
    - AFROTC, Commissioning, 1953 August
    - AFROTC, Commissioning, Senator Smith's son, 1953 January 29
    - AFROTC, Col. Knight and Dr. Edens, 1953 May
    - AFROTC, Review Preparations, 1953 May 1
    - AFROTC, Review, 1954 March 22
    - AFROTC, J. Barger Commissioning, 1954 January
    - AFROTC, Medal Award, 1954 May 5
    - AFROTC, Commissioning, 1954 July
    - AFROTC, Inspection, 1955
    - AFROTC, Rifle Competition, 1955
    - AFROTC, Col. Knight's Retiring Ceremony, 1956 January
    - AFROTC, Col. Todd and Col. Knight, 1956 January
    - AFROTC, Cadet Awards, 1956 November
    - AFROTC, Sgt. Norvell, 1956 June
    - AFROTC, Ballots for Military Ball Queen, 1956 March
    - AFROTC, Capt. Patterson, 1956 July
    - AFROTC, 1930 Group, 1957 January
    - AFROTC, Visiting General, 1957 February
    - AFROTC, Planning Review, 1957 June
    - AFROTC, Awards, 1957 June
    - AFROTC, Visiting General, 1957 October
    - AFROTC, St. Awards, 1958 March
    - AFROTC, Todd and Officer, 1958 March
    - AFROTC, 1958 April 13
    - AFROTC, Major C.F. Halsted and Col. Todd, 1958 June
    - AFROTC, Chart, 1960 July
    - AFROTC, Mid Term Commissioning, 1960 February
    - AFROTC, Cols. Todd and Duncan Medal Presentation, 1960 May
    - AFROTC, Staff, 1960 February
    - AFROTC, Military Inspectors, 1960 May
    - AFROTC, Col. Duncan and Dr. Hart, 1961
    - AFROTC, Inspectors, 1961 October
    - AFROTC, Chicago Tribune Awards, 1961
    - AFROTC, Ron Kotchen's Commissioning, 1961 September
    - AFROTC, Inspectors Gov., 1961
    - AFROTC, Vis., 1962 May
    - AFROTC, Graduation, 1962 June
    - AFROTC, A.F. Chaplain Roth Getting Award, 1962 November
    - AFROTC, Awards, Capt. Powell and Student, 1962 February
    - AFROTC, General J.D. Page, 1963 March
    - AFROTC, Major Richard Oldham, 1963 August
    - AFROTC, Award to Manchester, 1963 May
    - AFROTC, Review, 1966 May
    - AFROTC, Inspection, 1952 April 7
  - Subject: Alumni Affairs
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumni Admissions Advisory Committee, 1964 May
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumni Banquet, 1941
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumni Banquet, Durham County, 1941
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumnae Council Meetings and Officers
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumnae Council Meet, 1962 March
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumnae Banquet (1st Alumnae Weekend), 1938 April 1-2
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumnae Weekend, 1939, 1940, or circa 1942-1948
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumnae Weekend, 1940 April 5-7
    - Alumni Affairs, Fourth Annual Alumnae Weekend, 1941 March 28-30
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumnae Meeting, 1949 April 8
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumnae Weekend, 1950 April
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumnae Weekend, 1952 May
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumnae Weekend, 1953
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumnae Weekend, 1955 May
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumnae Weekend, 1955 May
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumnae Day, 1958 April
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumnae Day, 1962 April
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumnae Day, 1963 March
    - Alumni Affairs, Willard, Mrs., Alumnae President, 1951 June
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumnae Officers, 1956 May
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumnae Officers, 1960 April
    - Alumni Affairs, Brim, Kenneth (alumnus), 1954 June
    - Alumni Affairs, Dean, Gordon (alumnus), 1950 March 15
    - Alumni Affairs, Dunn, Albert (class of 1943)
    - Alumni Affairs, Flowers, Claude (alumnus), 1960 July
    - Alumni Affairs, Flowers, Claude, with Grandsons, 1960
    - Alumni Affairs, Jennings, Bill (alumnus), 1961 December
    - Alumni Affairs, Edwin Jones and Edens (award), 1956 October
    - Alumni Affairs, Justin Miller (alumnus), 1965 December
    - Alumni Affairs, Moore (alumnus), 1954 October
    - Alumni Affairs, Mumford, L. Quincy (alumnus), 1954 April 16
    - Alumni Affairs, Penfield, Add Sr. (alumnus), 1962 July
    - Alumni Affairs, Charles S. Rhyne (alumnus), 1955 June
    - Alumni Affairs, Townes, Charles (alumnus, Nobel Prize), 1967 March
    - Alumni Affairs, E.C. Perroro
    - Alumni Affairs, 25th Class Reunion Group Officers, 1946 October 5
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumni Officers Class of 1958, Alumni Register, 1958 April
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumni Officers, 1959 June
    - Alumni Affairs, St. Officers at Univ. H., 1961
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumni 1962-1963 President, 1962 May
    - Alumni Affairs, Past Presidents of the Alumni Association, 1966 October
    - Alumni Affairs, Bequest Meeting, 1960 November
    - Alumni Affairs, Bequest Meeting, 1960
    - Alumni Affairs, Sons and Daughters of Trinity Alumni, 1928-1929
    - Alumni Affairs, Sons and Daughters of Trinity Alumni, 1929-1930
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumni Family and Freshman Students, 1955 September
    - Alumni Affairs, Freshmen (Sons and Daughters of Alumni), 1955 September
    - Alumni Affairs, Frosh Sons and Daughters of Alumni, 1956 September
    - Alumni Affairs, Sons and Daughters of Alumni Dinner, 1957 September
    - Alumni Affairs, Children of Alumni (Frosh), 1958 September
    - Alumni Affairs, Frosh Dinner (Alumni), 1959 September
    - Alumni Affairs, Frosh Alumni Parents Luncheon, 1967 September
    - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1896 at 1936 Reunion
    - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1909
    - Alumni Affairs, Science Class of 1914-1915, 1955
    - Alumni Affairs, Trinity Class of 1918, 1968 May
    - Alumni Affairs, Miscellaneous Class
    - Alumni Affairs, Graduation Class of 1924, 1949 May 6
    - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1928, 1952 October
    - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1931 Reunion, 1955 October
    - Alumni Affairs, 1940 Class Reunion, 1965 April
    - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1943, 1968 May
    - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1944, 1970 August
    - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1953 Dinner, 1955 October
    - Alumni Affairs, 1959 Reunion Feature, Chanticleer, 1969 May
    - Alumni Affairs, Divinity Alumni Officers, 1958 November
    - Alumni Affairs, Divinity Alumni Officers, 1961 November
    - Alumni Affairs, Divinity Alumni Lunch (S. Smith, Speaker), 1963 October
    - Alumni Affairs, Divinity School Alumni Officers Dinner
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumni Officers, including: James L. Newsom, R. Percy Reade, Dan W. Umstead, Walter A. Biggs, Charles A. Dukes, L.S. Laprade, F.H. McGrannahan, John L. Moorhead, 1941 December
    - Alumni Affairs, Durham Engineering Alumni Officers, 1955 September
    - Alumni Affairs, Durham Engineering Alumni Officers, 1956 May
    - Alumni Affairs, Duke-Durham Fund, 1957 February [see also Town/Gown]
    - Alumni Affairs, Durham-Duke Fund Dinner, 1958 November
    - Alumni Affairs, Duke-Durham H.C. Committee, 1958 November
    - Alumni Affairs, Duke-Durham Alumni Dinner, 1959 December
    - Alumni Affairs, Duke-Durham Fund Dinner, 1961 November
    - Alumni Affairs, Duke Durham Dinner, 1961
    - Alumni Affairs, Duke-Durham Fund, 1962 November
    - Alumni Affairs, Duke-Durham Fund, 1967
  - Subject: Alumni Affairs (cont'd) (Box 2)
    - Alumni Affairs, Duke-Durham Fund, 1968 October
    - Alumni Affairs, Engineering Alumni Award to Ed Kray Bill, 1961 September
    - Alumni Affairs, Engineering Alumni Vis., 1957 February
    - Alumni Affairs, Engineering Alumni Officers, 1960
    - Alumni Affairs, Engineering Alumni Officers, 1963 October
    - Alumni Affairs, Engineering Alumni Officers, 1964 November
    - Alumni Affairs, Executive Committee, 1964 August
    - Alumni Affairs, Law Reunion Class of 1936, 1966 April
    - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1940 Law, 1965 May
    - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1941 Law, 1964 August
    - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1941 Law Reunion, 1966 April
    - Alumni Affairs, Law Alumni Council, 1963 November
    - Alumni Affairs, Law Alumni Council, 1965 May
    - Alumni Affairs, 10th Year Law Reunion Planning, 1961
    - Alumni Affairs, 1956 Law Class Reunions, 1966 April
    - Alumni Affairs, Loyalty Fund Dinner for Durham Merchants, 1949 June
    - Alumni Affairs, Loyalty Fund Feature for the Alumni Register, 1949?
    - Alumni Affairs, Loyalty Fund Officers, 1952 March 10
    - Alumni Affairs, Loyalty Fund Dinner Groups, 1956 September
    - Alumni Affairs, Loyalty Fund Dinner, 1956 September
    - Alumni Affairs, Class Agents Meeting, Loyalty Fund, 1956 October
    - Alumni Affairs, Loyalty Fund Committee Meeting, 1963 March
    - Alumni Affairs, Loyalty Fund Kickoff, 1958 October
    - Alumni Affairs, Family Alumni, 1955 June
    - Alumni Miscellaneous and Unidentified, 1969 March
    - Alumni Affairs, Chanticleer Class Copies, 1970 March
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumni Council Officers, including: R. L. Flowers, W.H. Wannamaker, Mrs. Augusta Walker Aydlett (1934), and W. B. Kiker (1909), 1945
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumni Executive Committee, National Council, 1955
    - Alumni Affairs, National Council Meeting, 1957 April
    - Alumni Affairs, Committee 1963 National Council Lunch, 1963 June
    - Alumni Affairs, National Council and General Alumni Dinner, 1966 June
    - Alumni Affairs, National Council Luncheon, 1966 December
    - Alumni Affairs, G.V. Allen, Knight, C.C. Jourdan, National Council Luncheon, 1966 December
    - Alumni Affairs, Plates
    - Alumni Affairs, Publications Board, 1961
    - Alumni Affairs, Alumni Publication Board, 1964 January
    - Alumni Affairs, New Employees, Alumni Department, 1968 December
    - Alumni Affairs, Mr. Duke's Birthday Party, Alumni, 1954 September
    - Alumni Affairs, Charles Dukes, Jr. (cap and gown), alumnus, 1955 June
    - Alumni Affairs, C.A. Dukes' Parents, 1958
    - Alumni Affairs, C.A. Dukes, Miller, and Ivey (alumni), 1961
    - Alumni Affairs, Wade, Herring, and Dukes addressing the L.A. Alumni Chapter by phone, 1947 August 1
    - Alumni Affairs, buffalo shirts, class of 1917, 1967 May
    - Alumni Affairs, alumni office staff working, 1951 January
    - Alumni Affairs, alumni office staff working, 1937-1941
    - Alumni Affairs, alumni registration and banquet, 1942
    - Alumni Affairs, committee, 1980 July
    - Alumni Affairs, Jack Baugh, 1970 August
    - Alumni Affairs, PJ Baugh
    - Alumni Affairs, Walter Biggs, 1971
    - Alumni Affairs, Phil Bolick, 1975 March
    - Alumni Affairs, Phillip Bolick, 1973
    - Alumni Affairs, Leo Brady, 1971
    - Alumni Affairs, Rubin Bressler, 1975
    - Alumni Affairs, Les Brown, 1985 February
    - Alumni Affairs, class of 1935, engineers
    - Alumni Affairs, Fred Chappell, 1969 November
    - Alumni Affairs, class of 1954, 1984
    - Alumni Affairs, CA Cannon
    - Alumni Affairs, chair, 1981 September
    - Alumni Affairs, Childress prints, 1969 August
    - Alumni Affairs, china plate, 1971 November
    - Alumni Affairs, class of 1952, 1976 October
    - Alumni Affairs, Pete Cruse, 1982 May
    - Alumni Affairs, Kathleen W. Dale, 1973
    - Alumni Affairs, Mrs. Frank Dalton, 1972 June
    - Alumni Affairs, Charles Dukes, 1981 January
    - Alumni Affairs, Charles A. Dukes, wife, families, 1983
    - Alumni Affairs, engineering alumni award, Alfred Hunt, 1980 March
    - Alumni Affairs, John A. Forlines, Jr., 1970 August
    - Alumni Affairs, John Forlines
    - Alumni Affairs, Lou Fracher
    - Alumni Affairs, alumni group, 1986 September
    - Alumni Affairs, Anne Garrard, 1981 January
    - Alumni Affairs, Erma Greenwood, 1971 June
    - Alumni Affairs, alumni group, 1977 January
    - Alumni Affairs, alumni group, 1978 July
    - Alumni Affairs, groups at Dean MG Wilson's retirement, 1970 April
    - Alumni Affairs, group
    - Alumni Affairs, RM Hardee
    - Alumni Affairs, Mrs. RK Harris, M. Adams, 1971
    - Alumni Affairs, Margaret Harris, 1970 August
    - Alumni Affairs, David Hartman, campus radio club, 1985 August
    - Alumni Affairs, Hewitt, 1965 June
    - Alumni Affairs, Joseph Hiatt, 1971 October
    - Alumni Affairs, Dan Hill, Jr., 1984 December
    - Alumni Affairs, Dan Hill, 1958 March
    - Alumni Affairs, Watts Hill, Sr.
    - Alumni Affairs, Alma Hull, 1970 August
    - Alumni Affairs, JM Hunt, Jr., 1958 June
    - Alumni Affairs, Joe Hunt, speaker of NC House, 1961 May
    - Alumni Affairs, Mac Hyman, 1954 June
    - Alumni Affairs, alumni institute, 1977 June 12
    - Alumni Affairs, first alumni institute class, 1975 June
    - Alumni Affairs, George Ivey, 1956 August
    - Alumni Affairs, Jan Blei Jason, 1987 September
    - Alumni Affairs, Laurence Johnson, 1985 January
    - Alumni Affairs, William B. Jones, 1979 July 10
    - Alumni Affairs, first alumni president, Lemuel Johnson, 1960 December
    - Alumni Affairs, Nathan Kaufman, 1975 December
    - Alumni Affairs, lecture series, 1972
    - Alumni Affairs, lecture series group, 1970
    - Alumni Affairs, Isobel Lewis, 1977 February
    - Alumni Affairs, A. London, Jr., 1975
    - Alumni Affairs, loyalty fund report, 1978 August
    - Alumni Affairs, Alex McMahon, 1970 September
    - Alumni Affairs, McCuller, class agent, 1954 October
    - Alumni Affairs, John McGovern, 1970 August
    - Alumni Affairs, Alex McMahon, 1973 March
    - Alumni Affairs, Lucy O'Brien Milner, 1970 June
    - Alumni Affairs, J. Meredith Moore
    - Alumni Affairs, William Murray, 1981 January
    - Alumni Affairs, Albert Myers
    - Alumni Affairs, JD Myers, 1975
    - Alumni Affairs, Virginia Neelon, 1980 September
    - Alumni Affairs, Fred Neu, 1984
    - Alumni Affairs, Jack Orr, 1974 June
    - Alumni Affairs, oldest alumni, 1956 May
    - Alumni Affairs, Pifer, engineering, 1972 September
    - Alumni Affairs, Marshall Pickens, 1970 January
    - Alumni Affairs, CW Poindexter, 1971 June
    - Alumni Affairs, planning session, 1970 July
    - Alumni Affairs, past presidents of alumni association, 1969 August
    - Alumni Affairs, Charles Rhyne
    - Alumni Affairs, John A. Snider
    - Alumni Affairs, Mrs. Smith, candidate for alumni office, 1972
    - Alumni Affairs, Doug Souchak, 1989 July
    - Alumni Affairs, Mrs. Marshall Spears, 1975 May
    - Alumni Affairs, H. Spence and wife, 1974
    - Alumni Affairs, Bob Stone, 1971
    - Alumni Affairs, Stryon, 1952 January
    - Alumni Affairs, William Stryon, 1971 September
    - Alumni Affairs, three generations, Gibbons, 1965 March
    - Alumni Affairs, US Steel CASE award to, 1985 July